signingsavvy.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy | ASL Sign Language Video Dictionary

## Privacy Policy

> ###  Your privacy is important to us.
> 
> **  
> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested.**
> 
> See the full details of our privacy policy below.

### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your browsing history. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

###  What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
**  
**
  * **To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested. **  
**  

  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for registration and order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account, in addition to receiving infrequent site news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

###  How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

###  Do we use cookies? 

Yes, we use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items during membership sign-up, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

###  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.** This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

###  Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

###  California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'My Account' page. 

###  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knownly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

###  Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms of Service agreement establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.signingsavvy.com/termsofservice>

###  Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy. 

###  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on May 20, 2013. 

###  Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**Email:** Use our [Contact Form](https://www.signingsavvy.com/contact) to send us an email.

**Mailing Address:**  
Signing Savvy  
2025 Central Park Drive #1009  
Okemos, MI 48805  
United States
